They're living lavishly.
They have a beautiful house.
They're living a luxurious life.
[SOBS] And now, they have your father too!
And what do we have?
Nothing!
Ma…
Someone definitely tried
to leak the files.
Tough luck for them,
all of our confidential data is encrypted.
Anyone tries to hack, leak our files,
this will pop up.
There's not much we can do here.
But I did my part,
so please delete the photos.
Not yet.
What?! Are you kidding me?
This is not what we talked about!
You said steal the files
and you'll delete the photos!
And that's what I did!
You really think you scare me, Peter?
Hmm?
If I were you…
I would behave.
Or else,
they will find out about you.
And I mean everybody.
[JORDAN]
So, wait. You think it's really him?
Dude, he invested 30 million in us.
It makes no sense if he actually
wants the company to fail.
Peter.
- Billy.
- Hi.
- Jordan.
Hi.
What brings you here?
Um…
Someone tried to leak
our confidential data.
Should I be worried?
No.
We just wanted to be
transparent with you, Peter.
- Uh, that's why we're here.
- [PETER] Right.
To inform you about the attempted leak
before you hear about it
from someone else.
We want you to hear from us first.
- Right, right.
- [JORDAN] Right?
Nothing to worry about.
Thank you. I… I appreciate that.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Thanks. Thanks.
I…
Listen. I… I gotta go.
[BILLY] Okay.
What?!
I warn you, Peter. Okay?
If you talk, I will ruin your life.
Mark my words!
[LUCY] You're going to see your eldest?
I'll see if she'll give me
a little more time.
After all, I don't have
much time left here anyway.
Maybe she'll…
You're going to tell her
about your illness
so she'll feel sorry for you?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Mariela?
What are you doing here?
Why?
Are you the only one
who can enter someone else's house?
Mariela, please.
Leave us alone.
You messed with our lives first.
If it had happened to you,
you'd be angry too.
So, do you regret what you did?
How did we mess with your lives?
What's your real problem
with me and my daughter?
You two are the problem!
So we won't stop
until we get what is rightfully ours!
What is rightfully yours?
I don't know what you're
talking about, Mariela.
This.
All of this.
This should've been ours.
Because my daughter and I have nothing.
Bea got nothing.
I refuse to let you live a good life here
while we're miserable!
If you don't leave, Mariela,
I'm going to call the police.
[PRECIOUS GRUNTS, GROANS]
[GRUNTS ANGRILY, HUFFS]
[MARIELA GRUNTS]
You don't deserve this life!
You're the ones who should be suffering!
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
[EXCLAIMS]
Come here!
[GRUNTS]
- [BOTH SHOUT]
- [KETTLE CLATTERS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MARIELA GRUNTS]
- [PRECIOUS GASPS]
- [THWACKS]
- [MARIELA GRUNTS]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ABIGAIL] Ma! Ma.
[MARIELA COUGHS]
Ma.
[ABIGAIL GRUNTS]
- Oh my God!
- Help!
Ma! Ma!
- Take her.
- Ma.
- Help her.
- Help! Ma.
Ma! Ma!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[FIRE CRACKLING IN DISTANCE]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [FIRE CRACKLING]
[LINE RINGING]
Precious.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Pick up.
Please, pick up!
[BUSY TONE]
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[BUSY TONE]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC SWELLS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You wrote this, right?
Yeah.
- But…
- I knew it.
But what's written there is true.
Yeah.
But you didn't write this
to express Robbie's feelings for me.
You wrote it to express your feelings…
for someone else.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But I don't get it.
What's holding you back?
Why can't you just be honest with her?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I mean, I'm telling you this
as your friend.
Do yourself a favor and talk to Billy.
And tell her how much you love her.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I think, boss, for now,
it's better if you just let her know that
you'll always be there for her.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FLAMES ERUPT]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[COUGHING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FIRE EXTINGUISHER HISSING]
- [FLAME ROARS]
- [PRECIOUS WHIMPERS]
[FIRE EXTINGUISHER CLINKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FIRE CRACKLING IN DISTANCE]
Oliver?
- Oliver.
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Wake up, Oliver.
- Billy?
- Get up.
- Huh?
Put these on.
- Billy! Oliver!
- Auntie?
The house is on fire! Let's go!
- Come on!
- Go! Go!
Be careful. Move!
- Billy.
- [COUGHING]
Auntie? [PANTS]
Billy, hold on.
Here, here, Billy.
- Wait here.
- Billy, hurry.
Use this to cover you and Oliver.
Let's go! Let's go! Hurry!
Wrap this around you.
Careful, Billy. Slowly!
[OLIVER COUGHS]
Do you think
there are still people inside?
What's going on here?
Billy's house is on fire!
They're still inside!
Careful, Billy!
[WOMAN] Sir, don't go in there!
- [MAN] Sir!
- Billy!
- [BILLY COUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
Oliver! Billy!
Oliver!
[MAN] Get a pail!
[WOMAN] Sir, the fire is spreading!
- [PRECIOUS] Oliver! Oliver!
- [BILLY] Auntie!
[PRECIOUS] Oliver! Oliver!
- Get out of here!
- [PRECIOUS] Hurry! Let's go!
[OLIVER] Billy!
- [CEILING THUDS]
- [BILLY GASPS]
[BILLY BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [ENRICO] Hold on! Move!
- [PRECIOUS COUGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [ENRICO GRUNTING]
- [METAL GATE CLANGING]
- Hurry! Get out!
- Oliver.
- Oliver!
- Auntie.
[BILLY SOBBING] Help!
- Oliver!
[BILLY SCREAMS] Help!
Oliver! Oliver!
- Auntie Pres!
- Jordan!
Jordan, Billy's still inside!
[ENRICO COUGHS]
[JORDAN BREATHES HEAVILY]
- Billy!
- [BILLY SOBBING]
Stay there!
- [JORDAN GRUNTS]
- [BILLY SOBBING]
Are you hurt?
Can you get up?
We're here! Sir, over here!
[JORDAN, BILLY COUGH]
Oliver! Oliver?
They're okay now. It's okay.
Billy.
We'll follow them.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
[VOICE TREMBLING] Okay.
[AMBULANCE DOOR CLOSES]
Okay. [SNIFFLES]
[SIREN WAILING]
[FIRE CRACKLING AGGRESSIVELY]
[BILLY SOBBING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOCTOR] Vital signs?
- Pulse 120, Doc.
BP, 130/80.
O2 sat, 82% on room air.
[DOCTOR] Possible smoke inhalation injury.
Transfer him to Trauma Bay 2 now!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
We've been able to stabilize
his vitals for now.
He's for further evaluation.
But he's still in critical condition.
Doc, why isn't he awake yet?
His blood sugar level dropped.
But we've corrected it already.
Let's give it time.
We will keep him under observation.
In the meantime,
I'll let you review the consent
for the limitations of
the procedures he'll undergo.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
How's your cough? You feel better now?
Hmm. How do you feel?
I'm okay.
You don't feel dizzy anymore?
Billy,
how is Papa?
He's okay.
He still needs to get better.
That's why you also need
to get better, okay?
You should rest, okay?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Lord God, thank you so much
for the blessing you've given us.
We'll share it among ourselves
while learning Your holy words.
In Jesus' name, amen.
- Amen.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Man, they already checked
the bars in the kitchen.
But it's bad news.
The metal is still sturdy.
But the railings
by the dumpster are corroded.
That'll be easier to destroy.
Okay?
- Amen.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[YOUNG BILLY] Please don't leave us, Dad!
Please don't leave.
[SOBBING] Please!
Mommy, please--
Don't waste your tears on worthless men.
We don't need him.
We can live without him.
[YOUNG BILLY SNIFFLES, SOBS]
[ENRICO] Please hear me out.
I know I did you wrong,
but forgive me, dear!
Dear, let me explain--
That's not necessary.
We're fine now.
Just leave.
Dear, I'm begging you.
No, I am begging you.
Let this be the last time
we see each other.
[BILLY SNIFFLES, BREATHES SHAKILY]
- [ENRICO COUGHING]
- [PRECIOUS] Oliver! Oliver!
- Get out of here!
- [PRECIOUS] Hurry! Let's go!
[OLIVER] Billy!
- [CEILING THUDS]
- [BILLY GASPS]
Billy.
Billy, the cops are here.
Okay.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Ma?
Ma.
Where have you been?
You weren't answering my calls.
Our problem is over.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you mean?
Now that Billy and her family are gone,
we've finally had our revenge
on the family
who took away your father.
And on your father as well.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
- Ma'am.
- Good evening.
I'll just give you the latest update.
We're still looking for Mariela Mercado
and her daughter, Beatrice.
We will let you know
as soon as we have any leads.
We've also obtained CCTV footage.
We already sent it to you.
Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks.
All right. Let's go.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
She kept on yelling.
She was yelling at me.
She said…
She said we took what's theirs.
If you hadn't stolen LoveFeast,
I wouldn't have thought
of something much better.
Okay, then.
I did steal it.
But the question is,
which one of us is the bigger thief?
A thief?
What the hell are you talking about?
If only you knew.
Bea told me the exact same thing, Auntie.
Do you think…
Billy, do you think Bea is aware
of what her mom is doing?
They came for LoveList.
And now our house too.
Who are they going to ruin next,
Auntie Pres?
You? Oliver?
My father?
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
CCTV footage revealed
a woman entering the property
shortly before the fire started.
Police have identified her
as Mariela Mercado.
[MARIELA]
Why should I be punished?
I'll find a way to get you out
of this. I'll protect you.
I'll do whatever it takes
to keep you out of jail, okay?
I'm sorry the condo is a bit small.
But we'll be fine here.
[BEA] You're Caloy's friend.
Wilfred, right?
[WILFRED] Looks like you and your mom
got caught up big time.
When are we going back
to the hospital?
Auntie Pres will be
looking after Dad.
Uh, just let me know if you need help
bringing Enrico's stuff to the hospital.
I need 10 million pesos in cash, or else!
That's too much, Bea!
You will give me 10 million pesos cash,
or bye-bye lawyer, bye-bye wife,
bye-bye family!